supportchoice.com 2014-02-21

# Privacy Policy | SupportChoice - Instant Computer Support

## Privacy Agreement

SupportChoice is sensitive to your concerns about how we use the personal information we collect from you through SupportChoice's website (the "Site"). SupportChoice takes your privacy seriously, and has implemented this privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") and internal policies and practices to keep your personal and financial information secure. The Privacy Policy covers SupportChoice's treatment of the Personally Identifiable Information we collect when you are on the Site and when you use SupportChoice services. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into Terms of Service, and therefore governs your use of the Site and SupportChoice services. By visiting the Site or using SupportChoice services, you accept the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you have questions or concerns about the Privacy Policy, please contact Customer Care at info@supportchoice.com. 

### What Information Do We Collect About Our Customers?

**Traffic Data.** SupportChoice uses a number of internal and third-party methods to recognize visitor data like IP addresses and browser settings (collectively "Visitor Data"). The SupportChoice internal servers and software automatically recognize Visitor Data. No Personally Identifiable Information is revealed in this process. The Site may use Visitor Data to compile traffic data about the types of visitors who use the Site at specific intervals (collectively "Traffic Data"). 

SupportChoice may use the standard cookie feature of major browser applications and third-party providers, or employ internally developed cookies and tracking codes, that allow SupportChoice to store a small piece of data on a visitor's computer about his or her visit to the Site. SupportChoice does not capture Personally Identifiable Information in cookies or use cookies to mine Personally Identifiable Information.  
We may use Traffic Data to analyze Site traffic, but this information is not examined for Personally Identifiable Information. 

We may also use Traffic Data to diagnose problems with our server, administer our Site, or display content according to your preferences. Visitor Data and Traffic Data may also be shared with business partners, affiliates, or advertisers on an aggregated and anonymous basis. 

**Personal Information.** SupportChoice requires each customer to provide us with personal information (collectively "Personally Identifiable Information") to access and use SupportChoice products and services. Personally Identifiable Information is captured only when a visitor accesses the Site, or speaks on the phone with a SupportChoice employee, and willingly discloses that information. This disclosure may occur when a visitor registers with the Site, engages in transactions, contacts customer service, or participates in contests, promotions, surveys, forums, content submissions, chats, bulletin boards, discussion groups, requests for suggestions, or other aspects of services offered by SupportChoice. 

Personally Identifiable Information includes: (i) "Contact Data" (such as your name, address, city, state, zip code, phone number, and email address); (ii) "Financial Data" (such as your credit card number, expiration date, and verification code); and (iii) "Demographic Data" (such as your zip code and sex). 

**Calls/Electronic Communications.** In the regular course of our business, SupportChoice may monitor and record phone conversations or email communications between you and SupportChoice employees for training and quality assurance purposes. We may receive a confirmation when you open or click on content in an email from us, which helps us make our communications to you more useful and interesting. If you do not wish to receive email from SupportChoice, you may unsubscribe from our mailing list on any of the emails we send. 

### How Do We Use the Information We Collect and Do We Share the Information We Receive?

We use information we collect from the Site to communicate with you, fulfill service agreements, facilitate your transactions with our third-party marketing partners, and inform you of offers and discounts. For example, you may receive a welcome email that confirms your username and password, and later receive communications responding to your inquiries, providing services you request, and managing your account. We occasionally send service-related announcements, for example, to alert you if we need to temporarily suspend the Site for maintenance. We may send promotional emails from time to time. Generally, you may not opt-out of service-related communications, which are not promotional. If you do not wish to receive service-related communications, you may terminate your account by telephone or email. However, you can opt-out of promotional communications by following the unsubscribe instructions in any communication or by emailing us at info@supportchoice.com. 

We share customer information with third parties only as follows: 

**Use of Personal Information.** SupportChoice, sometimes with the assistance of a third party or SupportChoice subsidiary, may use your Personally Identifiable Information to process your payment through merchant account services, to generate the products and services you order, and to analyze our customer demographics. Your Contact Data may be used to follow up with you on transactions you initiate on the Site, respond to inquiries made through the Site, inform you of changes to the Site, and send you additional information about SupportChoice and its products and services. Unless specifically authorized by you, we do not provide Personally Identifiable Information to third parties for marketing purposes. We may provide information to a third party in response to a subpoena or to otherwise comply with the law. 

Contact Data and Traffic Data are used to gather general statistics about our customers and visitors. We may use Demographic Data to generate collective information about our users, but not in a way that identifies any user specifically. For example, we may inform third parties about the number of registered users and unique visitors, and the pages most frequently browsed. 

**Opting Out.** You may choose not to provide SupportChoice with Personally Identifiable Information or you may turn off cookies in your browser by changing its settings. If you make these decisions, you may continue to visit the Site and browse its pages. However, SupportChoice cannot process orders without Personally Identifiable Information. 

Generally, you may not opt-out of service-related communications, which are not promotional. If you do not wish to receive service-related communications, you may terminate your account by telephone or email. 

If you would like to learn more or opt out of receiving online display advertising tailored to your interests, please visit the Networking Advertising Initiative at [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) or the Digital Advertising Alliance at <http://aboutads.info/choices>. If you delete your cookies, use a different browser, or buy a new computer, you will need to renew your online display advertising opt-out choice. 

**Website Areas Beyond SupportChoice's Control.** The Site may include interactive forums, such as message boards and chat rooms. Any Personally Identifiable Information disclosed in these areas is public and becomes public information. You should use caution when deciding whether to disclose your personal information in these forums. 

**Other Transfers.** We may share Personally Identifiable Information and other data with businesses controlling, controlled by, or under common control with SupportChoice. If SupportChoice is merged, acquired, or sold, or if some or all of our assets or equity are transferred, we may disclose or transfer Personally Identifiable Information and other data in connection with the associated transactions. 

**Bankruptcy.** In the event of a SupportChoice bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used. If such an event occurs, your Personally Identifiable Information may be treated like any other SupportChoice asset and sold, transferred, or shared with third parties, or used in ways not contemplated or permitted under this Privacy Policy, without notice to you or your consent. 

### Links

**Third-Party Websites and Third-Party Service Providers.** SupportChoice may maintain links to other websites and other websites may maintain links to the Site. This Privacy Policy applies only to SupportChoice and not to other websites accessible from SupportChoice or that you use to access SupportChoice, each of which may have privacy policies materially different from this Privacy Policy. If you visit other websites, SupportChoice is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those sites. It is your responsibility to review the privacy policies of non-SupportChoice websites to confirm that you understand and agree with them. 

We may work with third-party service providers that we do not own or control. Unless authorized by you, we do not provide your Personally Identifiable Information to any third-party service providers, except as explained in this Privacy Policy. 

### Accessing and Changing Your Account

**User Access to Order Information.** SupportChoice will give you, or anyone listed as a contact for your account, information about your order. This may include information about the nature and status of your order, information you provided to process your order, payment information, and contact information. For some products, we may provide information about your order to other individuals named in the order. We also may provide information to a third party in response to a subpoena or to otherwise comply with the law. 

**User Access to and Ability to Update Personally Identifiable Information.** You may visit your personal account profile at any time by logging in and clicking on the "My Account" link. Through My Account, you may: (i) review and update your Contact Data; If you want to remove your Personally Identifiable Information from our Site, you may contact us at info@supportchoice.com. SupportChoice may maintain some or all of this data in its archives even after it has been removed from the Site. 

### How Secure Is the Personal Information We Collect?

**Our Commitment to Data Security.** We strive to make certain that our servers and connections incorporate the latest encryption and security devices. We have implemented physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect. Credit card and personal information are transmitted by secure servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission is guaranteed to be 100% secure and we therefore cannot guarantee the security of information you transmit to or from the Site or using our services, and you provide this information at your own risk. ACCORDINGLY, WE DISCLAIM LIABILITY FOR THE THEFT, LOSS, OR INTERCEPTION OF, OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS OR DAMAGE TO, YOUR DATA OR COMMUNICATIONS. BY USING THE SITE AND OUR SERVICES, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU UNDERSTAND AND ASSUME THESE RISKS. 

**IF YOU BELIEVE YOUR PRIVACY HAS BEEN BREACHED THROUGH USE OF OUR WEBSITE, PLEASE CONTACT US IMMEDIATELY AT info@supportchoice.com.**
